Hello friends, I welcome you to Market Dues.
Friends, if you
are new to the channel, you can subscribe to the channel.
If you like the video, you
can also like the video and
share the video. Friends, in this video
we are going to cover two to three such
news of today which you will get
to see focusing directly on the stock. So, the
first news
that comes from Havells India Limited, so
what do you get to see in Havells India,
if seen today,
you are seeing a rise of 35 in it, a
rise of 3.31 is seen,
which is around 47 points. Its
price is also
trading at 171. So
what news are we getting to see in this,
we are getting to see the news
that Goldman Sachs has upgraded its target from its 52 week high,
so how much is your target, they have told you.
Goldman Sachs says that its
target should be 17 points upside from this price range.
Momentum can be seen,
which is the target,
your target becomes around 16660, your first target
will be 1540 and your second target becomes
₹1660, so next, if we talk about
i bank,
you are seeing a news coming in aaa bank today,
if you look at its chart pattern,
you will not see any change because there is no
news in it, there is no news of aaa bank
inside, they have bought the stake and
where did they buy the stake, aaa bank has
bought its positions in i Lombard, due to which
you are seeing a rise of around 4.5 at 4 today, the
price is currently trading at
₹1.28, so
how much stake did they buy in it,
IIC Bank has bought a stake of 1.4 in IIC Lombard,
these things have happened through a Y block deal and who are its sellers, they are from
Bharatiya Enterprises
Identification: These are the sellers. So far, this
identification has already
bought that stake in IIC Bank. So, there is nothing
big in it
because both these branches are the same, IIC
Bank and ICICI. There is only a work difference between them, everything
else is the same. This is
significant. How many lakh 69.7 lakh
shares have been sold here,
representing around 1.4 per cent.
In the calculation of percentage within equity, these things are
coming up. There has been a change of hands because someone has
sold, someone has bought. Bharatiya
Enterprise has sold, while IIC Bank has
bought. That is why you are seeing this change of hands. So, let us
focus on the chart of Lom Bard once to see if
we can get any such opportunity today.
If there are some such reasons, then what
opportunity can we see? Friends,
if you like our chart analysis, then
please give a thumbs up in the comment section.
If you do not like it, then give a
thumbs down once.
So that we don't analyze this chart again.
Some people like it, some
people don't. I will
see the ratio in the comments section, it will depend on that. If we
look at the ICC Lombard, you saw the volume decreasing recently here,
but the
volume of the breakout level was seen
increasing, you are seeing this a
little better. If we
look at it here, the price has hit a new all-
time high. Its previous
all-time high was almost around how many rupees.
If we look at the all-time high, it
was ₹1.75. And today
you have seen the market hitting another new high. So
today's
high is ₹1.34. So
we will have to wait for its monthly or weekly closing
if we want to find any opportunity
within it because we
don't jump in the middle. The reason for not jumping in the middle is simple, there is a
lot of risk involved.  It happens that
by jumping in the middle you have no risk, your
risk reward ratio does not match, that is
we do not prefer jumping in the middle, the
stock will go up a lot, it will not go
up and it will not
come in our control, there is no problem
but we will not incur any loss, we will have to
tread a little safely, if
we have to understand things, if we have to do something then we will have to
tread a little safely, if seen then we will get
its weekly closing also, still
our work will be done but there
should be some retesting, so next if we talk about
CMS Photex System, then
what news are you getting today in it, today
you are getting to see a decline of % in it,
you can consider this,
you are getting to see a mid-sized company, so
today's news in it is
that its promoters have
sold their equity of 27.1,
which is around 1594 crores, it has
changed hands, that is, they have sold it to someone else, so due to which
you can see the reason that  A significant fall of
around 10% was seen in this,
you may see this fall continuing tomorrow as well because
if something is happening in the company, then no
one can understand it better than the promoter, so
somewhere or the other the retail will
definitely be heavy on it,
why did the promoter sell it, you will get to see these things
and if you look at it according to its data, if
you
look at it quarterly, then you will get its data in quarterly time as to
who bought this stake, but there is no such
thing coming here that who bought it,
these things happened through bulk deal, so
next you are getting to see another big news
related to Adani Group, so
this news is being seen related to Adani Gup, it
is not a listed company, this news is being seen of Adani,
you are getting to see this news related to Adani Defence and Aerospace because
it is
not listed in the market, let us assume that it is a technology
which works in the defence sector, in the
defence and aerospace sector.  By looking at the name
you must be getting to know that
a company works in defense and aerospace,
so you have got to see a very big positive news in this
that Adani Group
Adani has invested 362 million
dollars which will be used to build two local
defense factories, they are going to build, what all is
manufactured in their defense factories, mostly
you will get to see that by
going to their website, it is also written recently here, so there is
no problem, there is
no need to go to the website, so
download,
you will get to know and see these things,
friends I hope you
liked the video, if you
liked the video then subscribe to the channel,
like the video,
share more videos, we will meet you
in the next similar video